Finding Aid for Executive Vice-President and Chief Financial Officer (University of Michigan) publications.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Investment Office
    - Reports
      - Review of Investments
        - 1956-1964 Review of Major Endowment Funds and Employees' Retirement Fund, 24 volumes (Box 22)
        - 1965-1969 Review of Major Endowment Funds and Employees' Retirement Fund, 10 volumes (Box 23)
        - 1970-1972 Review of Investment Programs of the Major Endowment Funds, Total Return Fund and Employees' Retirement Fund, 6 volumes (Box 23)
        - 1974 Review of Investment Programs of the Major Endowment Funds and Total Return Fund (Box 23)
      - Schedule of Investments
        - 1969-1989, 11 volumes (Box 23)
      - Survey of University Investment Policy, 1942 (Box 23)
    - Cambridge Associates Investment Reports 1988-1993
      - College and University Operating Funds: The internal Bank Concept 1988 (Box 26)
      - University of Michigan Diversification of Assets: Reorganization, Oil and Gas, and Venture Capital Investing (A Discussion Document) June 22, 1989 (Box 26)
      - University of Michigan Tactical Asset Allocation November 8, 1989 (Box 26)
      - The University of Michigan Market Update May 31, 1990 (Box 26)
      - Value Investing September 1990 (Box 26)
      - Distressed Company Investing September 1990 (Box 26)
      - Foreign Fixed Income Investing 1991 (Box 26)
      - University of Michigan Discussion Materials December 5, 1991 (Box 26)
      - University of Michigan Advisor's Meeting Discussion Materials January 28, 1992 (Box 26)
      - University of Michigan Advisor's Meeting Discussion Materials June 4, 1992 (Box 26)
      - University of Michigan Advisory Committee Meeting June 2, 1993 (Box 26)
  - Office of Financial Analysis and Cost Reimbursement
    - Budget Analyses
      - FY88 Budget Analyses and Final General Fund Cost Center Allocation Reports, 1988 (Box 23)
      - Fiscal Year 1988-1989 Budget Analysis, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Revenue Analysis (Box 26)
      - FY 1991-1995 Analysis of Revenues and expenditures by Department, Part One March 1996 (Box 26)
      - FY 1991-1995 Analysis of Revenues and expenditures by Department, Part Two April 1996 (Box 26)
  - AVPF Quality of Work Life and Recognition Team
    - Quality of Work Life Advantages and Possibilities (Box 26)
  - Financial Data Systems Task Team
    - Access Control Facility: Detail System Design Specification, May 1977 (Box 26)